Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lourdes Portillo Papers
1979¯2001
M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
150.0 Linear feet (113 cartons, 5 flat boxes, 9 special containers) still in process
Production materials from Lourdes Portillo's documentary film¯making career from 1979¯2001. Includes both pre¯ and post¯production paper records as well as moving image and audio materials from her productions.
Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences.
Corporation for Public Broadcasting.
Muñoz, Susana
Portillo, Lourdes
Q Productions.; Salinas de Gortari, Carlos; Selena, 1971¯1995
Collection contents
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Despues de Terremoto
    - Proposals: Introduction: Ms. Portillo's resume and other important information, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 1)
    - Proposals: Copyright registration application, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 2)
    - Proposals: Legal rights, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 3)
    - Proposals: Ownership rights, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 4)
    - Proposals: Partnership agreement, 1/1978; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 5)
    - Proposals: Distributor contract, 11/1983; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 6)
    - Proposals: License agreement, 1/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 7)
    - Proposals: Shipping/money matters, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Film budget, 3/1978; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 9)
    - Production: Synopsis in Spanish, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 10)
    - Production: List of crew and cast, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 11)
    - Production: Original storyboard, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 12)
    - Production: Original storyboard ¯ file #2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 13)
    - Production: Storyboard, cue sheets, notes: file #3 breakdown, pictures, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 14)
    - Production: Original screenplay: file #1, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 15)
    - Production: Original play: file #2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 16)
    - Production: Original play: file #3, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 17)
    - Production: Notes to crew, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 18)
    - Production: Shooting notes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 19)
    - Production: Shooting schedule, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 20)
    - Production: Contracts with crew, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 21)
    - Production: Labs #507, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 22)
    - Production: Sub¯titles: French & German, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 23)
    - Production: Subtitling ¯ Color Film Center, 11/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 24)
    - Press Packet: "Signature" poster for project, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 25)
    - Press Packet: Xochitl flyer for project, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 26)
    - Press Packet: Printed poster, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 27)
    - Press Packet: Original, 1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 28)
    - Press Packet: Black folder ¯ Press Packet, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 29)
    - Press Packet: Fondo Del Sol packet, 3/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 30)
    - Clippings/news articles in English: Caminos Magazine ¯ LA, CA, 11/1982; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 31)
    - Clippings/news articles in English: Daily News, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 32)
    - Clippings/news articles in English: Contemporary Cinema, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 33)
    - Clippings/news articles in English: Nuestro, 12/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 34)
    - Clippings/news articles in English: Various, 6/1982; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 35)
    - Clippings/news articles in Spanish: El Mexicano ¯ Juarez, Mexico, 10/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 36)
    - Clippings/news articles in Spanish: La Opinion, 11/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 37)
    - Clippings/news articles in Spanish: Various Spanish news clips, 1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 38)
    - Professional correspondence: Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences 52nd Annual Academy Award information, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 39)
    - Professional correspondence: Rudolfo A. Anaya, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 40)
    - Professional correspondence: Personal, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 41)
    - Professional correspondence: Letters of recommendation, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 42)
    - Professional correspondence: Complimentary letters, 1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 43)
    - Professional correspondence: Letters of intent to screen Terremoto, 1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 44)
    - Professional correspondence: Spanish correspondence, 1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 45)
    - Professional correspondence: Nicaraguan letters, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 46)
    - Professional correspondence: International correspondence, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 47)
    - Professional correspondence: Technical type correspondence, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 48)
    - Professional correspondence: Reject letters, 1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 49)
    - Distribution: Letter of representation: copyright, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 50)
    - Distribution: Distribution, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 51)
    - Distribution: Ruiz Productions, Inc., Hollywood, CA, 10/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 52)
    - Distribution: 1996 royalties, 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 53)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: 5th Festival International de Films de Femmes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 54)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Miami Int'l Film Festival ¯ USA, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 55)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Modern Language Film Festival ¯ Middlebury, VT, 8/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 56)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: San Antonio Cinefestival, San Antonio, TX, 7/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 57)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Festival de Documentals y Cortos ¯ Bilbao, Spain, 8/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 58)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Festival International ¯ Brussels, Belgium, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 59)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Cartagena International Film Festival ¯ Columbia, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 60)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Primer Festival del Nuevo Cine Latino Americano ¯ Cuba, 12/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 61)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Grenoble Shortfilm Festival ¯ Paris, France, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 62)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Oberhausen ¯ Germany, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 63)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Festival Bureau ¯ Poland, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 64)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Mostra Internazionale del Nuovo Cinema ¯ Roma, Italy, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 65)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: The 8th Film Festival ¯ Rotterdam ¯ Netherland, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 66)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Festivals Internationaux de Cinema ¯ Switzerland, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 67)
    - Letters of intent to exhibit: Festival International de Cinema Nyon ¯ Switzerland, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 68)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Selected film exhibits (black folder), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 69)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Chicano Film Festival ¯ flyer: UCSD¯ San Diego, CA, 2/1981; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 70)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Chicago Film Exhibition and Festival, East Michigan University, 4/1982; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 71)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Denver International Film Festival, Denver, Colorado, 5/1981; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 72)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: El Museo del Barrio, National Latino Film and Video Festival, NYC, NY, 6/1981; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 73)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Los Angeles International Film Expo, Los Angeles, CA, 3/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 74)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: San Francisco International Film Festival, San Francisco, CA, 8/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 75)
    - Festivals ¯ USA: Women Make Movies, Inc., NYC, NY, 6/1981; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 76)
    - International festivals: Lille Film Festival ¯ France, 9/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 77)
    - International festivals: Leipziger Film festival ¯ Berlin, Germany, 7/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 78)
    - International festivals: XXIX Internationale Filmwoche ¯ Germany, 10/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 79)
    - International festivals: Tradeshow Einladung ¯ Germany, 11/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 80)
    - International festivals: Latino bar ¯ Riminicinema ¯ Italy, 1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 81)
    - International festivals: Ibero Americano ¯ Spain, 12/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 82)
    - International festivals: Festival San Sebastian ¯ Spain, 1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 83)
    - International festivals: Thessaloniki International Film Festival, Greece, 3/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 84)
    - International festivals: Cinemateca Uruguaya ¯ Uruguay, SA, 3/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 55, Folder 85)
    - Screenings: The Advantages of Diversity, 6/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 86)
    - Screenings: The American Film Institute, 1/1979; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 87)
    - Screenings: Bay Area Filmmakers Showcase, San Francisco, CA, 5/1981; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 88)
    - Screenings: Bauer International Pictures, 4/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 89)
    - Screenings: Carlton College, Northfield, Minnesota, 5/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 90)
    - Screenings: A Celebration of Chicano Art, 8/1991; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 91)
    - Screenings: Cine Accion, San Francisco, CA, 11/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 92)
    - Screenings: El Universal, Denver, CO, 4/1981; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 93)
    - Screenings: Global Village, NYC, NY, 12/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 94)
    - Screenings: NABET, Berkeley, CA, 3/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 95)
    - Screenings: Pacific Film Archive, Berkeley, CA "Chicano Film Weekend", 4/1982; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 96)
    - Screenings: Post Vanguard Gas Station, NYC, NY, 1/1991; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 97)
    - Screenings: Roxie Cinema, San Francisco, CA, 4/1981; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 98)
    - Screenings: Third World Newsreel, NYC, NY, 1987; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 99)
    - Screenings: UCLA ¯ Los Angeles, CA, 5/1981; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 100)
    - Screenings: University Art Museum, Berkeley, CA, 8/1982; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 101)
    - Screenings: Whitney Museum of American Art 56: NYC, NY, 1/1991; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 102)
    - Seminars and conferences: Cine Sin Fronteras, UCLA, 5/1981; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 103)
    - Seminars and conferences: Comite Hispano Americano, San Francisco, CA, 1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 104)
    - Seminars and conferences: International Film Seminars, Inc.: 10th Public Television Seminar, Harriman, NY, 1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 105)
    - Seminars and conferences: Media and the Humanities, 12/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 106)
    - Seminars and conferences: US Conference for Alternative Cinema, NY, 6/1979; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 107)
    - Seminars and conferences: WETA: Hispanic Heritage Week, Washington, DC, 7/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 108)
    - Seminars and conferences: Women in the Director's Chair: Chicago, IL, 11/1982; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 109)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror, panelist, etc. Ms. Portillo as panelist, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 110)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror, panelist, etc. Ms. Portillo as president of jury, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 111)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror, panelist, etc. Minority Women Lecture Series, Davis University, CA, 2/1982; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 112)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror, panelist, etc. Northern California Women in Film and TV, Berkeley, CA, 5/1983; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 113)
    - Other: Ms. Portillo as juror, panelist, etc. "Visiting Artist" ¯ University of Colorado at Boulder, 2/1996; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 114)
    - Awards: 1983 Golden Gate Awards, San Francisco, CA, 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 115)
    - Awards: Somar Film Tribute: San Francisco, CA, 5/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 116)
    - Awards: List of tributes, awards, festivals, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 117)
    - Awards: Tribute to South of Market Filmmakers, San Francisco, CA, 5/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 118)
    - Awards: CABE 1980 Conference, workshop evaluation, 2/1980; 1.0 Folders (Carton 55, Folder 119)
    - "Terremoto" Master Catalogue, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 110, Folder 10)
    - "Terremoto" Print Lab Documentation, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 110, Folder 11)
    - "Despues del Terremoto" Lab Paperwork, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 111, Folder 11)
  - Las Madres: The Mothers of Plaza de Mayo
    - Proposals: Synopsis and Vital Data of Film, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 1)
    - Proposals: Information on Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 2)
    - Proposals: Information/Spanish Interview ¯ Lourdes Portillo, 1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 3)
    - Proposals: Susana Velarde Munoz' Bio & Resume, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 4)
    - Proposals: FAF Guidelines, 1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 5)
    - Proposals: Vanguard Application Summary, 9/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 6)
    - Proposals: Film Fund: Media Project Application, 2/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 7)
    - Proposals: Project Proposal ¯ Linea Fundadora, 2/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 8)
    - Proposals: National Community Funds Grant, 6/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 9)
    - Proposals: NEH Program Guidelines, 1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 10)
    - Proposals: Women's Opportunity Giving Fund, 6/1982; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 11)
    - Proposals: Limited Partnership Sample, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 12)
    - Proposals: Copyright Form, 9/1983; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 13)
    - Proposals: CPB (Corporation for Public Broadcasting) Program Fund, 12/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 14)
    - Proposals: Various Grants/Donations, 7/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 15)
    - Proposals: Levinson Foundation, Santa Fe, N.M., 6/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 16)
    - Proposals: Various Resumes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 17)
    - Budget: Rough Budget, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 18)
    - Budget, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 19)
    - Budget: Update, 6/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 20)
    - Budget: Update, 11/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 21)
    - Budget: Progress Report ¯ #1, 7/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 22)
    - Budget: Funding: The Women's Foundation, 3/1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 23)
    - Budget: Foundation Library Material: Various Contacts for Support, 1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 24)
    - Budget: Film ¯ Low Budget 8mm Info, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 25)
    - Budget: Funders' List/Main Credits List, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 26)
    - Budget: International Documentary Association Membership, Los Angeles, CA, 3/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 27)
    - Budget: Contribution Requests, San Francisco, CA, 1/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 28)
    - Budget: Income, 1984¯1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 29)
    - Budget: Contact List: Supporters, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 30)
    - Budget: Fund Raising ¯ Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes by Susana Munoz, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 31)
    - Expenses: Accounting Binder, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 32)
    - Expenses: Taxes, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 33)
    - Expenses: Debts, 1984¯1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 34)
    - Expenses: Bayview Bank Statements, 1985¯1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 35)
    - Expenses: Donation to FAF by Ms. Portillo, 11/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 36)
    - Expenses: 1983¯1985 Cancelled Checks, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 37)
    - Expenses: Individual Envelopes with Various Bills, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 38)
    - Expenses: 1984¯1988 Cancelled Checks, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 39)
    - Expenses: Research Mail Expenses, 1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 40)
    - Expenses: Various Expenses, 9/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 41)
    - Expenses: Condie & Lee, Oakland, CA, 11/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 42)
    - Expenses: Michael Anderson, 6/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 43)
    - Expenses: Monaco Lab, 1/1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 44)
    - Expenses: Invoice for Editing, 7/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 45)
    - Research, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 46)
    - Research: Renee Epelbaum, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 47)
    - Research: Renee Epelbaum, 5/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 48)
    - Research: Renee Epelbaum: Partial Narrative on Negative, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 49)
    - Research: Various Magazine/Newspaper Articles, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 50)
    - Research: The Independent Film & Video Monthly ¯ NY, NY, 1/1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 51)
    - Research: Nicaragua in Struggle, 7/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 52)
    - Research: Latin American Perspectives, 6/1978; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 53)
    - Research: Alicia Partnoy: "The Little School ¯ A Secret Detention Camp in Argentina", 1983; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 54)
    - Research: Testimony on Secret Detention Camps in Argentina, 2/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 55)
    - Research: Metamorfosis, 1980¯1981; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 56)
    - Research: Areito: Nuevo Cine Latinoamericano ¯ Cuba, 1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 57)
    - Research: Xhisme Arte, 2/1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 58)
    - Research: Cineaste, 1975; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 59)
    - Production: Partial Script: Handwritten By Lourdes, 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 60)
    - Production: Synopsis: Final English Narration, 8/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 61)
    - Production: English Transcript, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 62)
    - Production: Update ¯ Progress Report of 5/85 & 7/85, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 63)
    - Production: English Narration, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 64)
    - Production: Spanish Transcripts, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 65)
    - Production: Spanish Version, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 66)
    - Production: German Version, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 67)
    - Production: German Tv Cue Sheet, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 68)
    - Production: Transcript of Final English Cut (Dialogue), 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 69)
    - Production: Paper Materials in AV Boxes 2 & 3, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 97, Folder 70)
    - Production: Edit Outline, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 1)
    - Production: Edit List, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 2)
    - Production: Music: Letters of Authorization, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 3)
    - Production: Music Cue Cards, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 4)
    - Production: Titles: Madres, 8/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 5)
    - Production: List of Subtitles, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 6)
    - Production: Excerpts: English, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 7)
    - Production: Excerpts: Spanish, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 8)
    - Production: Main Credits, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 9)
    - Production: Typesetting, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 10)
    - Production: Publicity Layouts, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 11)
    - Production: Miscellaneous Notes: Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 12)
    - Production: 1994 Production Costs, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 13)
    - Production: 1996 Post Production Bills ¯ Various, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 14)
    - Professional Correspondence: Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes of Susana & Lourdes, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 15)
    - Professional Correspondence: Susana Blaustein Munoz' Personal & Professional Letters, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 16)
    - Professional Correspondence: Spanish Correspondence, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 17)
    - Professional Correspondence: The American Film Institute, Los Angeles, CA, 3/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 18)
    - Professional Correspondence: Other Correspondence, 1986¯1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 19)
    - Professional Correspondence: Writers Guild of America, West, Inc. ¯ LA, CA, 1/1979; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 20)
    - Professional Correspondence: Letters of Support, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 21)
    - Professional Correspondence: Letters of Commitment, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 22)
    - Professional Correspondence: Complimentary Letter: New World Pictures ¯ LA, CA, 7/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 23)
    - Professional Correspondence: Letters from the Bay Area ¯ Read Books: Palo Alto, CA, 8/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 24)
    - Professional Correspondence: Mr. Seymour Wishmore ¯ San Francisco, CA, 1/1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 25)
    - Professional Correspondence: Genevieve Lefebvre ¯ Paris, France, 8/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 26)
    - Professional Correspondence: European Correspondence: Pending, 1980; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 27)
    - Publicity: Original Leaflet for Mill Valley Film Festival, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 28)
    - Publicity: Original Press Packet, 10/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 29)
    - Publicity: Publicity Lay¯Out, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 30)
    - Publicity: Press Packet, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 31)
    - Publicity: Press Packet with Critical Data, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 32)
    - Publicity: Publicity, 7/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 33)
    - Publicity: News Clips ¯ Various, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 34)
    - Publicity: Selected Film Exhibitions, 1985¯1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 35)
    - Publicity: List of Worldwide Festivals, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 36)
    - Publicity: Sundance Poster, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 37)
    - Publicity: The American Documentary ¯ NYC, NY, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 38)
    - Publicity: P.R. Various Press, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 39)
    - Publicity: Original Press Kit Info, 1984¯1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 40)
    - Publicity: Press Packages ¯ Synopsis, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 41)
    - Publicity: Layout & Original Press Kit, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 42)
    - Publicity: Mailing List, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 43)
    - Publicity: Ms. Magazine ¯ Boulder, CO, 7/1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 44)
    - Publicity: POV: Publicity ¯ NY, NY, 6/1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 45)
    - Travel: 1993¯1994, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 46)
    - Travel: 1994 & 1996, 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 47)
    - Travel: Tickets & Souvenirs, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 48)
    - San Francisco Chronicle ¯ San Francisco, CA, 10/1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 49)
    - San Francisco Examiner, Image Magazine ¯ San Francisco, CA, 2/1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 50)
    - P.R. ¯ Various Press, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 51)
    - Gramma ¯ Havana, Cuba, 12/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 52)
    - The Independent ¯ NY, NY, 5/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 53)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian ¯ S.F., CA, 4/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 54)
    - Newspaper Articles ¯ Wall St. Journal & L.A. Times, 7/1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 55)
    - Various News Clips ¯ #1, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 56)
    - Various News Clips ¯ #2, 1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 57)
    - News Clips ¯ Spain, 1985; 1.0 Items (Carton 98, Folder 58)